原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     草草  小酸奶  白夜君  苏葵
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     西·查
后期     吉吉
总监     小酸奶
深入黑暗  第一季 第九集
别碰我
Get the fuck off me.
爱  玩  梦
你怎么知道她没救了
How do you know that there's no way to save her?
你不是上帝
You're not God!
内森
Nathan!
你要杀死她了
You're just the one who's killing her!
他们来敲门
敲敲门
是谁
黑眼孩子  在你的窝里
他们在夜晚游荡  寻找事端
偷盗灵魂  就像小偷
但转身时  请注意
他们会把你们引出去  他们很会耍诡计
佚名
我们为什么停下了
Why have we stopped?
有种奇怪的东西叫人类
There's these weird things called human beings
我们午餐时会饿的
and we get hungry at lunch time.
就这破地方吗
Here, this shithole?
算了吧  我就不去了
Yeah, no thanks, I'll sit this one out.
爸爸说五分钟内进去
Dad said be inside in five minutes.
关上门
Close the door!
这多棒
How nice is this?
我们三个一起上路
Three of us on the open road.
我们有三个人吗
There's three of us?
乖一点
Be nice.
爸爸  她恨我们
Dad, she hates us.
她不恨我们
She does not hate us.
她就是到青春期了
She's just a teenager.
这年纪就这样
Kind of goes with the territory.
等你到了她的年纪时就会理解了
You'll understand one day when you're her age.
如果我那么情绪化就杀了我好了
Kill me if I ever get that moody.
你俩啊
I swear
真是太不一样了
you two couldn't be more different,
但你们又都像你们的妈妈
and yet you're both just like your mama.
她会喜欢这样的
She would have loved this.
爸爸
Dad?
我不希望你死
I don't want you to die.
我哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
如果发生了坏事呢
What if something bad happens?
不会发生坏事的
Nothing bad is gonna happen.
我保证
I promise.
拉钩发誓
Pinky swear?
来吧
Come on.
父亲节特餐免费
要我给你续杯吗
Would you like me to top it off?
安静
Be quiet.
灵力需要最大程度的精神集中
Psychic powers require maximum focus.
你举着
You're holding up...
三根手指
Three fingers!
错了
Wrong.
-你作弊了  -你才作弊了
- You cheated! - You cheated!
你本来举着三根手指  但你放下了一根
You had three fingers and you put one down.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
你肯定是透过手指偷瞄了
That means you were peeking through the fingers then.
我才没透过手指偷瞄
I was not peeking through my fingers.
-那你怎么知道的  -你变了
- Then how did you know? - You switched it.
你怎么知道的  你有灵力吗
How do you know, are you psychic?
你是说你真有灵力
So you're saying that you're actually a psychic.
或许是呢
Maybe I am, maybe I am.
好吧  那告诉我
All right, then I need to know
这周末谁能赢得比赛
who's gonna win the game this weekend.
-给  亲爱的  -谢谢
- Here you go, honey. - Thank you.
非常感激
Thank you so much.
你真不想要点吗
You sure you don't want anything?
-不  -薄煎饼呢
- Nope. - Want some pancakes?
不要  我不饿
Nope, I'm not hungry.
你还好吗
You feel okay?
嗯
Yup.
你打算吃点薄煎饼
You gonna have any pancake
就那么多的糖浆  还是...
with your syrup, or you're just...
直接喝糖浆了
gonna go straight liquid?
别乱说我  我喜欢糖浆
Don't judge me. I like syrup.
要不要我打开盖子
Do you just want me to take the lid off
你好直接都倒在上面
so you can just pour it all directly straight on there?
那或许会简单些
Might be easier.
怎么了
What?
你是怕有人偷走它吗
Are you afraid someone's gonna steal it?
怎么  让你不爽吗  茜茜
Why, does it bother you, Sissy?
首先  内森
Firstly, Nathan,
你可以别喊我"茜茜"吗  我不是7岁了
can you not call me "Sissy" because I'm not seven.
父亲节这天你都不能喊他爸爸吗
Can't you call him "Dad" even on Father's Day?
你还记得
You remembered!
好了  你给我准备了什么
All right, what'd you get me?
超级大的拥抱
A super big hug.
少来了
Get out of here.
-你想抱吗  -天呐
- You want a hug? - Oh my God.
你...别
You-- oh-- no!
你们好奇怪
You guys are so weird.
父亲节快乐
Happy Father's Day.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
看啊
Look at that.
父亲节奶昔
A little Father's Day milkshake.
勃杜克酒庄  玛尔戈红葡萄酒
深表同情
您可以看到
As you can see,
我们的容器选择很多
we have a wide range of receptacles.
你们觉得呢  孩子们
What do you think, girls?
都好难看
They're ugly.
我觉得她一个都不会喜欢的
I don't think she'd have liked any of them.
她有什么特别喜欢的颜色吗
Is there a particular color that she was fond of?
她一向喜欢好红酒
She always loved a good red.
勃杜克酒庄  玛尔戈红葡萄酒
棉花糖
失踪
女士
Miss?
零钱不用找了
Keep the change.
失踪
J
我受不了了
没事的  亲爱的  我保证
你跟我们一起坐前面吧
Why don't you ride up front with us?
我喜欢后面
I like it back here.
不颠吗
Isn't it bumpy?
你给我买棉花糖了吗
Did you get my marshmallows?
这里安静
It's quiet.
但不怎么安全
But it's not that safe.
谢谢你的理解
Thank you so much for your understanding.
我觉得这样不合法
I don't think it's legal.
别撞到路上的坑了
We'll try not to hit any potholes!
别闹了
Cut it out!
就是这里了
So this is the-- the spot.
真美丽  是吧
It's really something, isn't it?
没有信号
There's no service.
你要给我们讲那个故事吗
Are you gonna tell us the story?
17年前  我认识你们妈妈时
So, 17 years ago, when I met your mama,
我们一起公路旅行
we took a road trip
就走的我们现在走的这条路
following the same path we're on now.
一样的加油站  一样的餐馆
Same gas station, same diner.
妈妈吃薄煎饼了吗
Did Mom have the pancakes?
当然了
You know she had the pancakes.
我们不知道我们要去哪
See, we didn't know where we were goin',
我们就是想这样
and that was kind of the idea.
我们只想在开阔公路上
We just wanted to be on the open road,
自由自在
total freedom.
我们停在了这里
So we stopped here.
一起喝了一瓶酒
We drank a bottle of wine together.
然后我带你妈
And then I walked Mom...
站在了克莱尔站的那个地方
right there where Claire's standing...
我没有戒指什么的  但
I didn't have a ring or anything, but...
我向她求婚了
I asked her to marry me.
没有
So, no,
这里本来没什么特别的
there wasn't anything special about this place.
但现在它特别了
But there is now.
我们就让她在这里安息
And this is where we'll lay her to rest.
迟了一年
Yeah, about a year late.
好了
All right.
我们收拾行李吧
Let's get unpacked.
小玛  你去拿上外套吧
Mags, why don't you grab your jacket
这里有点冷了
since it's gettin' a little chilly?
也拿我的外套来
Grab mine too, would you?
亲爱的
Hi baby.
我要六点之后才能下班回家
I'm not gonna be back from work till after six,
所以你可以给玛姬做点晚饭吗
so can you please make Maggie some dinner?
冰箱里有意面
There's pasta in the fridge.
你只需要加热就行
All you have to do is literally just heat it up.
我睡觉前会回去的
I will be back for bedtime.
爸爸也会回去  但你知道他的厨艺什么样
Dad'll be home, but you know what his cooking is like.
还有
And...
昨晚的事抱歉
I'm sorry about last night.
我们吵得毫无意义
That was a stupid fight.
我知道你爱我的
I know you love me.
我也爱你
And I love you.
好了  我得走了
Okay, I gotta go.
我爱你  亲爱的
I love you, sweetheart.
快点  你在里面待一小时了
Hurry up, you've been in there an hour!
等一下  玛格特
One second, Maggot!
无网络服务
该死
Oh, fuck.
短信未能发送  请检查信号
有人吗
Hello?
妈妈
Hey Mom.
我们来到你和爸爸最爱的地点了
We made it to you and Dad's favorite spot.
好想你
Miss you.
你还好吗
You okay?
我很好
I'm good.
帮我做晚饭啊
Help me make dinner?
好  就去
Sure, in a second.
好
Okay.
你是电影里的吗
Are you in a movie?
你是女人吗
Are you a woman?
不是  等等
No. Wait.
不是
No.
你是人类吗
Are you human?
不是
Nope.
你是机器人吗
Are you a robot?
是的
Yes.
你最好的朋友也是机器人吗
Is your best friend a robot?
可能吧
Maybe.
你最好的朋友
Does your best friend
会指使你吗
boss you around?
-是的  -天呐
- Yep. - Oh my God.
快说出来吧
Just say it already!
你...
Are you...
R2D2吗
R2-D2?
爸爸又赢了
Dad wins once again!
震惊啊
Shocker...
你就是大姨妈了才这么尖酸
You're just bitter 'cause you're on your period.
好了
All right.
天呐  我不知道
Oh God, I don't know
你和妈妈怎么受得了这里
how you and Mom could stand it out here.
六月份还这么冷
It's freezing and it's June.
是啊
Well...
我们还有彼此嘛
We had each other
我们偎依在了一起
and we snuggled.
爸爸
Hey Dad?
我能闻闻你的啤酒吗
Can I smell your beer?
你能闻闻我的啤酒吗
Can you smell my beer?
别激动  我只是好奇
Don't get excited, I'm just curious.
闻起来像克莱尔
It smells like Claire.
闭嘴  玛格特
Shut up, Maggot.
茜茜
Hey Sissy?
内森
Nathan?
你在写什么
What you writing?
可能是给她傻逼男朋友的信
Probably a letter to her stupid boyfriend.
你来到这世上
Were you put on this earth
就是逼我自杀的吗
to make me wanna kill myself?
如果是的话  你会自杀吗
If I was, would you do it?
你的睡觉时间是不是过了
Isn't it past your bedtime?
我没有睡觉时间  你的睡觉时间是不是过了
I don't have a bedtime. Isn't it past your bedtime?
你有睡觉时间  因为我没有
Yeah, you do, No, 'cause I don't have one.
-我没有睡觉时间  -你有
- I don't have a bedtime.  - Yes you do!
-你有  我没有  -别扔
- Yes-- no I don't! - Don't!
我没有睡觉时间  你承认了
I don't have a bedtime, you admit it!
这个男孩
So this boy.
他很特别吗
Is he special?
对我来说是的
To me he is, yeah.
那为什么不让我们见见
Then why haven't we met him?
因为我想让他喜欢我
Because I want him to like me.
怎么了
What?
我的嘴唇很干  我还没有唇膏
My lips are dry and I don't have any chapstick.
你妈妈和她的口红
Your mom and her lipstick.
我不知道你还记不记得  你当时还小
I don't know if you remember. You were little.
但你以前经常和你妈妈坐在一起
But you used to sit with your mom,
你们俩都坐在镜子前
both of you plopped down in front of the mirror,
然后一起化妆
and you guys would put on your makeup together.
是的  我记得
Yeah, I remember.
妈妈看起来很漂亮
Mom looked so beautiful.
但是...
And...
我看起来像个小丑
I looked like a clown.
可爱的小丑
Cute clown.
妈妈真是太美了
Mom was gorgeous.
是的  她是
Yes, she was.
克莱尔
Claire!
-茜茜  -别碰我
- Sissy.  -Get the fuck off me.
我也不想让她走  克莱尔
I didn't want to let her go, Claire.
你必须知道这点
You have to know that.
我不想谈论这个
I don't wanna talk about this.
你怎么知道她已经没救了
How do you know that there's no way to save her?
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
这是我这辈子做的最艰难的决定
It was the hardest decision I've ever had to make
我知道你们俩...
knowing that you two girls--
我说了  我不想谈论这个
I said that I don't want to talk about this.
你不是上帝  内森
You're not God, Nathan!
是你杀了她
You're just the one who's killing her!
克莱尔
Claire.
我们得谈谈这事
We have to talk about it.
她当时已经很痛苦了  亲爱的
She was in so much pain, honey.
这不是这趟旅途的目的
That's not what this trip is about.
我只想让你...
I just want you to...
亲爱的  别进去
Sweetheart, don't go inside.
克莱尔
Hey Claire.
Claire!
我不知道如何弥补  瓦尔
I don't know how to fix this, Val.
茜茜
Sissy?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
宝贝
Honey?
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
没事的
Hey, shh, it's okay.
来  躺下吧
Come on, let's lie down.
你没事的  睡吧
You're okay. Come on.
怎么了  宝贝
What is it, honey?
有人在车顶上
There's somebody--there's someone on the roof!
-什么  -我看见...
- What? - I saw--
我看见有人...
I saw someone just--
刚刚在...
Just now on the...
什么
What?
宝贝  没人能上去  什么...
Baby, nobody can get up there. What--
爸爸
Dad?
-出什么事了  -我不知道
- What is that? - I don't know.
过来坐在你姐姐旁边
Come over and sit down next to your sissy.
有人吗
Hello?
我们有枪的
We've got a gun in here.
请让我们进去
Please let us in.
谁在外面
Who's out there?
爸爸
Dad?
没事的  宝贝  没事的
It's okay, honey, all right?
天哪
Jesus.
请你们开开门吧
Please will you open the door?
有什么事
What's the problem?
我们想给你们看个东西
We want to show you something.
他们看起来好奇怪
They look really weird.
别开门
Don't.
如果他们真的需要帮助怎么办
What if they really need help?
闭嘴  玛姬
Shut up, Maggie!
别开门
Don't...don't open it.
我在加油站见过她
I saw her at the gas station.
我觉得她在跟踪我们
I think that she followed us.
那里离这里有80公里
That was like 50 miles back!
听着...
Listen, um...
我们不能让你们进来
We can't let you in.
因为已经很晚了
You know, it's late.
如果你们需要电话
If you guys need a phone,
你们可以去高速上
uh, you might want to make your way up to the highway.
我们最终会让你们出来的
We'll make you come out eventually.
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
我觉得她们走了
I think they're gone.
你又不知道
You don't know that.
-她们只是孩子  -闭嘴  你个小...
- It's just kids.  - Shut up, you little--
-克莱尔  -怎么了
- Hey, Claire! - What?
你把我们带来这里
You dragged us all the way out here,
而现在我们被困在一个不知名的地方
and now we're stuck in the middle of nowhere
还不知道外面有什么
with who knows what outside.
只是想告诉你
Just so you know,
没人想来这趟旅行
nobody wanted to go on this trip.
克莱尔  这趟旅行是为了妈妈
Claire, this trip was for Mom.
是啊  可是你猜怎么着
Right, well, guess what?
妈妈死了
Mom's dead.
小玛  你可真行
Mags-- real nice.
小玛
Hey Mags.
宝贝
Honey.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我得确定她们走了
I'm gonna go make sure they're gone.
-别去  -你为什么不过去
- Don't go-- - Why don't you go back there
向你的妹妹道歉
and apologize to your sister?
玛姬  你能出来吗
Maggie, can you come out?
玛姬
Maggie...
走开
Go away!
玛姬  对不起
Maggie, I'm sorry.
玛姬
Maggie.
我觉得她们走了
Think they're gone.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好了  二位
All right, guys.
希望我们把她们吓跑了
Hopefully we scared 'em off.
我们回去睡觉吧
Let's go back to bed.
那里吗  不行
There? No.
绝对不行
No way.
你想睡床吗
Do you want to take the bunk?
那你呢
What about you?
我继续放哨
I am gonna keep watch.
以防那些混蛋再来敲门
In case those punks come knocking again.
我们要打得她们满地找牙
We'll give 'em a mouthful of teeth.
休息会儿吧
Get some rest.
明天是个重要的日子  对吗
Tomorrow's a big day, okay?
好了
All right.
克莱尔
Hey, Claire.
来吧
Come on.
没事的  来吧
It's okay, come on.
是那两个孩子干的
The kids?
还能是谁
Who else?
-操他妈的  -注意言辞
- Fuck! - Watch your mouth.
好吧
All right.
高速路就在几公里外
Highway's just a few miles back.
我一有信号  就打电话叫人来帮忙
Soon as I get reception I'll call for help
否则我就叫人来帮我们
or I'll flag somebody down.
你要把我俩留在这里吗
You're leaving us here?
小玛走不了那么远
Mags can't make that hike.
车的事别告诉她
And don't tell her about the truck.
希望我能在她醒来之前回来
Hopefully I'll be back before she wakes up.
我需要你在这里陪你妹妹
I need you to stay here with your sister.
如果她们回来了怎么办
What if they come back?
那你要跑进拖车把门锁上
You're gonna get in that trailer and you're gonna lock the door
在我回来之前待在里面
and you're gonna stay in there till I get back.
好吗
Okay?
测试测试
One, one, one, one, one.
好的
Okay.
好  你们俩待在拖车里
All right, you guys just stay in the trailer.
我会在早饭前回来  好吗
I'll be back before breakfast, okay?
怎么了
What is it?
没什么
Um, it's, uh, nothing.
-你确定吗  -确定
- You sure? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
致妈妈
你过得怎么样  我们正在旅行
我现在很困惑
这趟旅途太悲伤了
如果你能回来的话
这是最蠢的一次旅行
我想你了  妈妈
你在干什么
What are you doin'?
不关你的事
None of your business.
告诉你男朋友  没有他你活不下去吗
Telling your boyfriend you can't live without him?
你想干什么
What do you want?
爸爸在哪里
Where's Dad?
他去爬个山
Uh, he went for a hike.
他说他会在早饭的时候回来
He said he'll be back for breakfast.
我饿了
Well, I'm hungry now.
他为什么不叫醒我
And why didn't he wake me up?
我就会和他一起去了
I would have gone with him.
他说他想让你留在这里
He said that he wanted you to stay here,
而且是他说了算  所以...
and he's the boss, so...
你向我隐瞒了什么事情
Something's going on you're not telling me.
我不是小孩子
I'm not a kid.
你就是个小孩子
Yes, you are a kid.
你想用对讲机联系他吗
Okay, do you want to try him on the walkie?
我想
Yeah.
就...
Just...
爸爸  你收到了吗  完毕
Dad, do you read? Over.
我是玛姬
It's Maggie.
试着再说一次"完毕"
Try saying "Over" again.
我是玛姬  完毕
It's Maggie. Over.
他为什么不回答
Why isn't he answering?
你在吗  完毕
You there? Over.
他肯定走出范围了
Uh, he must be out of range.
你不知道
You don't know that.
如果他迷路了呢
What if he got lost?
或摔倒了
Or fell?
或被蛇咬了
Or got bit by a snake?
你知道响尾蛇一秒就能
Did you know rattlesnakes can strike up to three meters
窜出三米多吗
in under one second?
-玛姬  -那比爸爸跑得快多了
- Maggie-- - That's way faster than Dad can even move.
玛姬
Maggie, it...
会没事的  好吗
It'll be fine, okay?
去穿衣服吧
Just go and get dressed.
内森  你在吗
Nathan, you there?
还担心吗
Still worried?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
他马上会回来的
He'll be back soon.
我能玩吗
Can I play?
这不是玩具
It's not a toy.
没有妈妈的人偶吗
No figure of Mom, huh?
做得很好
It's really nice.
你这么认为吗
You think so?
你一直带在身边吗
Do you keep it with you all the time?
嗯  那又怎样
Yeah, so?
我觉得这很机智
I think that's really smart.
这样妈妈就能一直照顾你了
That way Mom can always look out for you.
想帮我在院子里做个狗屋吗
Want to help me make a dog house for the yard?
我们没有狗
We don't have a dog.
是的  但小女孩能做梦
No, but a girl can dream.
好吧
Okay.
已经做好了狗的脸
Made the dog's face so far.
狗是蓝色的
The dog's blue.
-对  -好吧
- Yeah. - Okay.
有人吗
Hello?
玛姬  你饿了吗
Maggie, getting hungry?
玛姬
Maggie?
玛姬  你在哪里
Maggie, where are you?
玛姬
Maggie?
该死
Shit.
玛姬  这不好玩
Maggie, this isn't funny.
玛姬
Maggie?
妈的
Fuck.
玛姬
Maggie?
有人吗
Hello?
救命
旅店  商场
玛姬
Maggie?
谁在外面
Who's out there?
请让我们进去
Please let us in.
我们有枪的
We've got a gun in here.
请你们开开门吧
Please will you open the door?
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
我们最终会让你们出来的
We'll make you come out eventually.
克莱尔
Claire?
克莱尔  你能听见吗
Claire, do you hear me?
我们能进来吗
*嘘  小宝贝*
*Hush, little baby*
*一句话也别说*
*Don't say a word*
*妈妈要给你买一只知更鸟*
*Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird*
玛姬
Maggie?
-玛姬  -*别唱*
- Maggie. - *Don't sing*
*妈妈要给你买一只钻石戒*
*Mama's gonna buy you a diamond ring*
玛姬
Maggie?
有人吗
Hello?
克莱尔
Claire!
*再见  宝贝*
*Rock-a-bye, baby*
*在树梢*
*On the treetop*
*当风吹起*
*When the wind blows*
*摇篮摇荡*
*The cradle will rock*
克莱尔
Claire?
玛姬
Maggie?
克莱尔
Claire!
*宝贝掉下来*
*And down will come baby*
你想让我回来
You wanted me back.
我就在这
Now here I am.
到妈妈身边来
Come to Mommy.
救命
Help!
内森
Nathan!
救命
Help!
内森
Nathan!
克莱尔
Claire!
救命
Help!
过来  过来
Hey, come here, come here.
没事了  没事了  没事了
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
里面有东西
There's something in there.
看起来像妈妈
It looked like it was Mom,
然后
and...
我觉得我要疯了
I think I'm going crazy.
我来  我只是  我来找玛姬
I was-- I was just-- I was looking for Maggie,
-因为她  -玛姬
- because she-- - Maggie?
-她离开了  -玛姬在哪
- She left the-- - Where's Maggie?
-她离开了拖车  然后我  -玛姬在哪  克莱尔
- She left the trailer and I-- - Where's Maggie, Claire?
我不知道  我不知道  她...
I don't know, I mean, I don't know, she--
什么叫你不知道
What do you mean you don't know?
玛姬
Maggie!
玛姬  宝贝
Maggie, baby!
玛姬
Maggie!
-玛姬  -爸爸
- Maggie? - Dad.
你他妈之前去哪儿了
Where the fuck were you?
别说脏话
Stop cussing.
过来  过来
Come here, come here.
我以为听到了你的声音  所以出去了
I thought I heard you outside and I went out there.
我还丢了一个人偶
And I lost one of my figures.
听着  你不能离开拖车
Listen, you cannot leave this trailer.
我不在时  要听克莱尔的
When I'm gone, Claire's in charge.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
这是你的娃娃
Here's your doll.
你说过你不会离开我  你保证过的
You said you'd never leave me, you promised.
玛姬  我正在回来的路上
Maggie, I was coming back.
我只是想找信号
I was just trying to go find signal.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
听着  除非和我在一起  否则不许离开拖车
Listen, you cannot leave this trailer unless you're with me.
你俩都是
That goes for both of you.
我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
我们走不了
We can't leave.
卡车发动不起来
Truck won't start.
所以我们在这过夜
So, we'll stay here tonight.
明天一早
And then tomorrow morning,
我们三人一起走到大路上去
all of us will hike up to the road.
那和妈妈道别呢
What about saying goodbye to Mom?
她得等等了
She's gonna have to wait.
我今天之前出去时
When I went on the hike earlier today,
找到一辆拖车
I found a trailer
里面有个死人
and there was a dead man inside of it.
他怎么了
What happened to him?
他  他自杀了
He, uh, he killed himself.
但我觉得他是被那些孩子害死的
But I think those kids made him do it.
好像那些孩子在刺激他出去
It's like they were daring him to go outside.
我们能进去吗
她们想要什么
What do they want?
我不知道
I don't know.
你为什么去垃圾场
What made you go to the junkyard?
玛姬不见了  我听见那边传来她的声音
Maggie was missing and I heard her voice up there.
我找到了她的娃娃
I found her doll.
我不知道这是怎么回事
I don't understand what's going on.
我觉得她们想引我们出去
I think they're trying to lure us out.
如果她们今晚来敲门
If they come knocking again tonight,
你俩别离开拖车
you two do not leave this trailer.
无论如何都不行
No matter what.
欢迎回家
你在做什么
What you workin' on?
一个派对
A party.
是吗
Oh yeah?
什么派对
What kind of party?
妈妈回家时的欢迎派对
A welcome home party for Mom.
这里有什么
What do we have here?
她肯定会喜欢的
Oh, yeah, she'd love that.
这些是灯吗
Are they the lights?
辛格尔
粉色的  我想她会喜欢
It's pink, I thought she would like it.
你觉得这些太闪了吗
Do you think these are too sparkly?
有"太闪了"这种说法吗
Is there a such thing as too sparkly?
这是个惊喜  所以别说漏了
And it's a surprise, so don't say anything.
快到睡觉时间了
It's almost bed time.
我们能收拾下  明天完成吗
Can we clean this up and finish tomorrow?
好吧
Okay.
带着玛姬  去厕所
Grab Maggie, go to the bathroom,
待在那里
stay there.
爸爸
Dad?
你和姐姐先过去
You go back with your sister,
我马上回来  好吗
and I'll be right back, okay?
你保证吗
Promise?
我保证
Promise.
把门锁上
Lock the door.
好  来吧
Okay, come on.
爸爸没事吧
Is Dad okay?
我们有枪
We've got a gun!
如果你们继续胡闹
If you guys don't quit messing around,
会有人挨子弹
somebody's gonna get killed.
你能陪我玩吗
Will you play with me?
你弄疼我了
You hurt me.
他怎么这么久
What's taking him so long?
好吧
Okay.
让我进去吧
Just let me in.
不
No!
克莱尔
Claire.
克莱尔  你能听见吗
Claire, can you hear me?
克莱尔
Claire?
听见了  我们在
Yeah, yeah, we're here.
你们还好吧
Are you guys okay?
还行吧
Kind of, yeah.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还行吧
Kind of.
我被困在这辆车里了  但我没事
I'm trapped in the truck, but I'm okay.
听着  我还是不知道她们想要什么
Listen, I still don't know what they want,
但是只有我们邀请她们才能进来
but they can't come in unless you invite them, okay?
不  不  不  爸爸
No, no, no. Dad!
我们听不到  爸爸
We can't hear you. Dad!
不要乱跑
Just stay put.
喂
Hello?
克莱尔
Claire?
他为什么不应
Why isn't he answering?
他为什么不回答我们
等等  待在这里
Hang on, just stay here.
什么  不
What? No!
-锁好门  -不  别走
- Lock the door. - No, don't go!
我  我得到通讯范围内
I just-- I have to get within range,
我马上回来  我保证
I'll be right back, I promise.
两分钟  给我两分钟
Two minutes, give me two minutes.
克莱尔  你能听到吗
Claire, can you hear me?
你能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
你能听到吗
克莱尔
Claire?
内森
Nathan?
Nathan.
内森
你能听到吗  内森
Can you hear me, Nathan?
内森
Nathan?
克莱尔
Claire.
让我进去
Just let me in.
妈妈
Mommy!
玛姬
Maggie.
你为什么不能那么做
Why can't you do it?
为什么
Why?
你真是太自私了
You're so fucking selfish.
离我们远一点
Stay the fuck away from us!
你甚至都保护不好我们的宝宝
You can't even protect our babies.
那不是小瓦
That's not Val.
我能进来吗
Can I come in?
滚开
Leave us alone!
那不是小瓦
That's not Val.
拜托  拜托
Come on, come on.
怎么了  玛姬宝贝
What's the matter, Maggie bear?
你不想和妈妈一起玩吗
Don't you want to play with mama?
你不能疯  不
You are not going crazy. No.
你不是真的
You're not real!
我是因为你才死的
You are the reason I'm dead.
真的是你吗  妈妈
Is it really you, Mommy?
当然是我  宝贝
Of course it's me, baby.
克莱尔
Claire?
克莱尔  你能听到我说话吗
Hey, Claire-- Can you hear me?
我爱你
I love you.
我以为你永远离开了
I thought you were gone forever.
-你为什么丢下我们  -玛姬
- Why did you leave us? - Maggie?
妈妈  我好想你
Oh, Mommy, I missed you!
我就在这里
I'm right here.
玛姬  你在和谁说话
Maggie, who are you talking to?
克莱尔  你能听到吗
Claire, can you hear me?
让我进来  宝贝
Just let me in, my love.
克莱尔
Claire.
Claire?
玛姬
Maggie.
玛姬  开门
Maggie, open the door.
玛姬
Maggie.
玛姬  开门
Maggie, open the door!
玛姬
Maggie!
你们这群小混蛋
Hey, you little motherfuckers.
来啊
Come on.
想玩吗
You wanna play?
来啊  来啊
Come on in, come on!
开门  克莱尔
Unlock the door, Claire!
来啊  宝贝
Come on, baby.
没事的  没事的
It's okay, it's okay.
玛姬  玛姬在哪里
Maggie? Where's Maggie?
-玛姬  -她在浴缸里
- Maggie? - She's in the tub.
她在浴缸里  她死了
She's in the tub, she's dead.
-什么  -她死了
- What? - She's dead.
玛姬
Maggie?
出来吧  亲爱的
Come on out, honey.
玛姬
Maggie!
亲爱的
Honey?
她本来就在这里
She was right here.
我看到了她的尸体
I saw her body.
这就是他们希望你这么认为的
That's what they want you to think, honey.
玛姬
Maggie!
他们想要的是孩子们
They're after the kids.
跟我们一直都没有关系
Never had anything to do with us.
-什么  -来
- What? - Come on.
-什么  -一直都与我们无关
- What? - It was never about us.
他们想要的一直都是玛姬
They wanted Maggie all along.
快来
Come on.
玛姬
Maggie?
Maggie!
克莱尔  快来
Claire, come on!
玛姬
Maggie!
但我看到了妈妈
But I saw Mom.
我也看到了妈妈
I saw Mom, too.
不仅仅是那样
It's not just that.
玛姬  我也听到她隔着门和她说话
Maggie, I heard her talking to her through the door.
这是他们和我们玩的游戏  亲爱的
It's just games they're playing with us, honey.
听着
Okay, listen!
我觉得她是想和我们说些什么
I think she's trying to tell us something.
-你为什么拿了这个  -我不知道  我只是...
- Why'd you bring this? - I don't know, I just--
来啊  爸爸
Come on, Daddy!
玛姬
Maggie!
-玛姬  -来啊  爸爸
- Maggie! - Come on, Daddy!
-我在这里  爸爸  -亲爱的
- I'm over here, Daddy! - Honey?
你抓不到我的
You'll never catch me!
玛姬
Maggie?
Maggie!
爸爸  来抓我啊
Daddy, come get me!
你抓不到我的
You'll never catch me!
玛姬
Maggie?
-来  -我不
- Come on. - I can't.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
好吧  我马上回来
Okay, I'll be right back.
内森
Nathan?
克莱尔
Claire?
玛姬
Maggie?
你来了
You're here.
你为我回来了
You came back for me.
你不是真的
You're not real.
玛姬在哪里
Where's Maggie?
她在这里
She's here.
她很安全
She's safe.
为什么
Why?
你背叛了我们
You betrayed us.
我们一家
Our family.
我
Me.
你放任我死去
You let me die.
-为什么  内特  -小瓦
- Why, Nate? - Oh, Val.
你当时很痛苦
You were suffering.
你放弃了
You gave up.
现在你还想要扔掉关于我的记忆
And now you're trying to throw my memory away.
不
No.
我不想
I don't want to.
你不需要
You don't have to.
我们又能在一起了
We can be together again.
我们又能一家团聚了
We can be a family again.
和我一起留在这里
Stay here with me.
内森
Nathan...
我不希望你担心我
I don't want you to worry about me.
照顾好彼此
Take care of each other.
内森
Nathan!
向我保证
Promise me,
到时候
when the time is right,
放我走
you'll let me go.
你不是我的小瓦
You're not my Val.
我的瓦莱丽已经死了
My Valerie's gone.
内森
Nathan!
-是克莱尔  -内森
- That's Claire.  - Nathan!
不  不
No, no, no!
克莱尔
Claire?
把瓶子扔给我  克莱尔
Throw me the bottle, Claire!
爸爸
Dad!
放我走
You have to let me go.
照顾好彼此
Take care of each other.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
做我们来这里要做的事
What we came here to do.
玛姬
Maggie.
快
Come on.
-玛姬  -爸爸
- Maggie... - Daddy!
没事了  没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
爸爸  他们把我抓走了
Daddy, they got me!
来  让我看看
Here, let me see.
-你没事吧  -我看到妈妈了
- You okay? - I saw Mommy.
她也在  她在拖车外
She was there, she was outside of the trailer,
我看到她了  她要我和她走  我就走了
I saw her, and she told me to come with her and I did.
不  那不是妈妈
No, that wasn't Mommy.
我好害怕  爸爸
I was so scared, Daddy.
我知道
I know.
但是你没事了
Shh, but you're okay.
你没事了  我们在一起
You're okay, we're together.
没事了
It's okay.
我们下次出游
Next time we go on a trip,
能不能安稳地住在旅店里
can we just stay in a hotel?